https://www.arslan.com/pages/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
In order to process your order and obtain authorization from the USPS Uniform Program, we will ask you for certain necessary information, such as your name, mail address, telephone number, email address, and shipping and billing information. In addition, we may, from time to time, ask for information related to an online survey, participation in a sweepstakes offer, or subscription to a newsletter or mailing list.
The information you provide is kept confidential and, subject to this policy, will only be used to support your customer relationship with us. We use a third party intermediary to perform certain order-processing functions. Any information we provide to this third party intermediary is used for the sole purpose of order processing. The information provided by you is not disclosed to any outside organization unless required by law or other regulatory authority.
If another entity acquires us or substantially all of our assets, the personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information we have about you will be transferred to and used by this acquiring entity. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.
Like many companies, we use "cookie" technology to keep track of your shopping cart. The cookie does not contain any personal information about you and is not used for any other purpose.
We also collect certain information from visitors and customers of our website, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, improve the quality of our service and administer our website. Aggregate usage and volume statistics may be provided to third parties.
We generally keep this policy posted on our website. You should review this policy frequently, as it may change from time to time without notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy.
WHEN YOU USE OUR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY STOP USING OUR SERVICES.
About Us
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Terms of Sale
Site Map
©
Arslan Uniforms, all rights reserved
Prices, terms and guarantees subject to change without notice.
